Guide to the Portland Reporter Photographs Collection 1960-1964
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- People Files, 1960-1964; Series B
  - Gen--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 72/27)
  - Geo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 72/28)
  - Gep--, 1963 (Box-folder 73/1)
  - Ger--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 73/2)
  - Ges--, 1961 (Box-folder 73/3)
  - Get--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 73/4)
  - Big--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 73/5)
  - Gie--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 73/6)
  - Gif--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 73/7)
  - Gil--, 1961--1964 (Box-folder 73/8)
  - Gil--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 73/9)
  - Gim--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 73/10)
  - Gin--, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 73/11)
  - Gir--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 73/12)
  - Gis--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 73/13)
  - Gis--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 73/14)
  - Githens, 1962 (Box-folder 73/15)
  - Giv--, 1960; 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 73/16)
  - Gje--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 73/17)
  - Gla--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 196473/18)
  - Gle--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 73/19)
  - Glenn, John, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 73/20)
  - Gli--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 73/21)
  - Glo--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 73/22)
  - Gmasz, 1961 (Box-folder 73/23)
  - Goa--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 73/24)
  - Gabel, 1961 (Box-folder 73/25)
  - Gac--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 73/26)
  - God--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 73/27)
  - Goe--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 73/28)
  - Gof--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 73/29)
  - Goh--, 1963 (Box-folder 73/30)
  - Gol--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 74/1)
  - Gol--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 74/2)
  - Goldwater, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 74/3-5)
  - Gon--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 74/6)
  - Goo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 74/7)
  - Goo--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 74/8)
  - Gor--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 74/9)
  - Gos--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 74/10)
  - Got--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 74/11)
  - Gou--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 74/12)
  - Gove, 1963 (Box-folder 74/13)
  - Gow--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 74/14)
  - Gra--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 75/1-2)
  - Gra--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 75/3)
  - Gra--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 75/4)
  - Gre--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 75/5)
  - Gre--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 75/6)
  - Gre--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 75/7)
  - Gre--, 1960; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 75/8)
  - Gri--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 75/9)
  - Gri--, 1961-1964-- (Box-folder 75/10)
  - Gro--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 76/1)
  - Gru--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 76/2)
  - Gua--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 76/3)
  - Gudman, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 76/4)
  - Gue--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 76/5)
  - Gulfer, 1961 (Box-folder 76/6)
  - Gui--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 76/7)
  - Gul--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 76/8)
  - Gum--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 76/9)
  - Gun--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 76/10)
  - Guppy, 1964 (Box-folder 76/11)
  - Gur--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 76/12)
  - Gus--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 76/13)
  - Gut--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 76/14)
  - Guy--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 76/15)
  - Guilliam, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 76/16)
  - Gwynne, 1964 (Box-folder 76/17)
  - Gyani, 1964 (Box-folder 76/18)
  - Gyes, 1964 (Box-folder 76/19)
  - Haa--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 76/20)
  - Hab--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 76/21)
  - Hac--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 76/22)
  - Had--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 76/23)
  - Hae--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 76/24)
  - Haf--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 76/25)
  - Hag--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 76/26)
  - Hah--, 1962 (Box-folder 76/27)
  - Hai--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 76/28)
  - Hakim, 1964 (Box-folder 76/29)
  - Hal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 77/1)
  - Hal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 77/2)
  - Hal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 77/3)
  - Ham--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 77/4)
  - Ham--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 77/5-6)
  - Han--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 77/7-10)
  - Han--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 78/1-2)
  - Har--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 78/3)
  - Har--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 78/4)
  - Har--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 78/5)
  - Har--, 1962 (Box-folder 78/6)
  - Har--, 1963 (Box-folder 78/7)
  - Har--, 1964 (Box-folder 78/8)
  - Har--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 78/9)
  - Har--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 78/10)
  - Har--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 79/1)
  - Har--, 1964 (Box-folder 79/2)
  - Har--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 79/3)
  - Has--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 79/4)
  - Hat--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 79/5)
  - Hat--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 79/6)
  - Hatfield, Mark, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 79/7-9)
  - Hau--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 80/1)
  - Hav--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 80/2)
  - Haw--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 80/3)
  - Hay--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 80/4)
  - Hay--, 1961; 1962 (Box-folder 80/5)
  - Hay--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 80/6)
  - Haz--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 80/7)
  - Hea--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 80/8)
  - Heb--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 80/9)
  - Hec--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 80/10)
  - Hed--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 80/11)
  - Heestand, 1962 (Box-folder 80/12)
  - Hef--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 80/13)
  - Heg--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 80/14)
  - Hei--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 80/15)
  - Hel--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 80/16)
  - Hem--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 81/1)
  - Hen--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 81/2)
  - Hen--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 81/3)
  - Hep--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 81/4)
  - Her--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 81/5)
  - Her--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 81/6)
  - Hes--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 81/7)
  - Het--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 81/8)
  - Hevia, Carlos, 1961 (Box-folder 81/9)
  - Heu--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 81/10)
  - Hew--, 1960-1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 81/11)
  - Hey--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 81/12)
  - Hib--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 81/13)
  - Hic--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 81/14)
  - Hid--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 81/15)
  - Hie--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 81/16)
  - Hig--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 81/17)
  - Hil--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 81/18)
  - Hil--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 81/19)
  - Himmelfarb, 1962 (Box-folder 81/20)
  - Hin--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 82/1)
  - Hir--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 82/2)
  - His--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 82/3)
  - Hit--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 82/4)
  - Hixon, undated (Box-folder 82/5)
  - Hje--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 82/6)
  - Hjo--, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 82/7)
  - Hlavka, 1961 (Box-folder 82/8)
  - Hoa--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 82/9)
  - Hob--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 82/10)
  - Hoc--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 82/11)
  - Hod--, 1969-1964 (Box-folder 82/12)
  - Hoe--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 82/13)
  - Hof--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 82/14)
  - Hof--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 82/15)
  - Hog--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 82/16)
  - Hoh--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 82/17)
  - Hoiland, 1961 (Box-folder 82/18)
  - Hokkanen, 1962 (Box-folder 82/19)
  - Hol--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 82/20)
  - Hol--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 82/21)
  - Hol--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 82/22)
  - Hol--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 83/1)
  - Hol--, 1964 (Box-folder 83/2)
  - Hol--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 83/3)
  - Hom--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 83/4)
  - Hon--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 83/5)
  - Hoo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 83/6)
  - Hop--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 83/7)
  - Hor--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 83/8)
  - Hor--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 83/9)
  - Hos--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 83/10)
  - Hou--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 83/11)
  - How--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 83/12)
  - How--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 83/13)
  - Hoxha, 1962 (Box-folder 83/14)
  - Hoy--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 83/15)
  - Hrabal, 1964 (Box-folder 84/1)
  - Hre--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 84/2)
  - Hruska, 1963 (Box-folder 84/3)
  - Hisia, undated (Box-folder 84/4)
  - Hsueh, 1963 (Box-folder 84/5)
  - Hub--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 84/6)
  - Huc--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 84/7)
  - Hud--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 84/8)
  - Hue--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 84/9)
  - Huf--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 84/10)
  - Hug--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 84/11)
  - Hui--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 84/12)
  - Huk--, 1960 (Box-folder 84/13)
  - Hul--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 84/14)
  - Hum--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 84/15)
  - Humphrey, Hubert, 1964 (Box-folder 84/16)
  - Hun--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 84/17)
  - Hun--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 84/18)
  - Hur--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 84/19)
  - Hus--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 84/20)
  - Hut--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 84/21)
  - Hux--, 1962 (Box-folder 84/22)
  - Huydee, 1962 (Box-folder 84/23)
  - Hya--, 1960 (Box-folder 84/24)
  - Hyd--, 1960-1961; 1964 (Box-folder 84/25)
  - Hyer, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 84/26)
  - Hys---, 1962 (Box-folder 84/27)
  - Hyun-Chul, 1962 (Box-folder 84/28)
  - Iakovos, 1962 (Box-folder 85/1)
  - Ibs--, 1962 (Box-folder 85/2)
  - Ichihashi, 1964 (Box-folder 85/3)
  - Ickes, 1961 (Box-folder 85/4)
  - Ida, 1926 (Box-folder 85/5)
  - Iddings, 1962 (Box-folder 85/6)
  - Ide, 1961 (Box-folder 85/7)
  - Idle, 1936 (Box-folder 85/8)
  - Idzal, undated (Box-folder 85/9)
  - Ier--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 85/10)
  - Ikeda, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 85/11)
  - Ile--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 85/12)
  - Ill--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 85/13)
  - Il-Kwon, 1964 (Box-folder 85/14)
  - Imel, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 85/15)
  - Imm--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 85/16)
  - Imper, 1964 (Box-folder 85/17)
  - Imthurn, 1962 (Box-folder 85/18)
  - Ing--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 85/19)
  - Inman, 1961 (Box-folder 85/20)
  - Ino--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 85/21)
  - Inskeep, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 85/22)
  - Ionesco, 1964 (Box-folder 85/23)
  - Iosue, 1961 (Box-folder 85/24)
  - Irly, 1916 (Box-folder 85/25)
  - Ire--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 85/26)
  - Irish, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 85/27)
  - Irvine, 1962 (Box-folder 85/28)
  - Irw--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 85/29)
  - Isa--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 85/30)
  - Isenstadt, 1963 (Box-folder 85/31)
  - Ish--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 85/32)
  - Isotalo, 1961 (Box-folder 85/33)
  - Israelson, 1961 (Box-folder 85/34)
  - Istomin, 1963 (Box-folder 85/35)
  - Itkin, 1964 (Box-folder 85/36)
  - Ito, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 85/37)
  - Itschner, 1964 (Box-folder 85/38)
  - Itterley, 1963 (Box-folder 85/39)
  - Iturbi, 1962 (Box-folder 85/40)
  - Iva--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 85/41)
  - Ive--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 85/42)
  - Ivory, 1963 (Box-folder 85/43)
  - Ivy, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 85/44)
  - Iwa--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 85/45)
  - Iyinde, 1961 (Box-folder 85/46)
  - Izumo, 1962 (Box-folder 85/47)
  - Izq--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 85/48)
  - Jab--, undated (Box-folder 85/49)
  - Jac--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 85/50)
  - 1960-1963 (Box-folder 85/51)
  - Jac--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 86/1)
  - Jac--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 86/2)
  - Jae--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 86/3)
  - Jaf--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 86/4)
  - Jag--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 86/5)
  - Jah--, 1961 (Box-folder 86/6)
  - Jaiswal, 1964 (Box-folder 86/7)
  - Jalbert, 1961 (Box-folder 86/8)
  - Jam--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 86/9)
  - Jan--, 1960-1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 86/10)
  - Jaques, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 86/11)
  - Jar--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 86/12)
  - Jastremski, 1963 (Box-folder 86/13)
  - Javits, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 86/14)
  - Jea--, 1962 (Box-folder 86/15)
  - Jef--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 86/16)
  - Jemison, 1964 (Box-folder 86/17)
  - Jen--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 86/18-20)
  - Jep--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 86/21)
  - Jer--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 86/22)
  - Jes--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 87/1)
  - Jet--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 87/2)
  - Jew--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 87/3)
  - Jiannini, 1961 (Box-folder 87/4)
  - Jimers, 1963 (Box-folder 87/5)
  - Jachimsen, 1962 (Box-folder 87/6)
  - Jackson, Vernon, 1963 (Box-folder 128/37)
  - Jaehnk, 1963 (Box-folder 87/7)
  - Jofre, 1963 (Box-folder 87/8)
  - Joh--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 87/9)
  - Joh--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 87/10)
  - Joh--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 87/11)
  - Joh--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 87/12)
  - Joh--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 87/13)
  - Joh--, 1960-1961; 1963 (Box-folder 87/14)
  - Joh--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 87/15)
  - John XXIII, Pope, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 87/16)
  - Johnson, Lydon B., President, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 88/1)
  - Johnson, Lydon B., President, 1963 (Box-folder 88/2-3)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (family), 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 88/4)
  - Joiner, 1964 (Box-folder 88/5)
  - Jol--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 88/6)
  - Jon--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 88/7-9)
  - Jor--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 88/10)
  - Jos--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 88/11)
  - Jotisalkara, 1962 (Box-folder 88/12)
  - Jau--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 88/13)
  - Joxe, 1961 (Box-folder 89/1)
  - Joy, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 89/2)
  - Julia, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 89/3)
  - Jud--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 89/4)
  - Juel, 1916 (Box-folder 89/5)
  - Juh--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 89/6)
  - Juilfs, 1963 (Box-folder 89/7)
  - Jul--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 89/8)
  - Jum--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 89/9)
  - Jun--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 89/10)
  - Jur--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 89/11)
  - Jus--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 89/12)
  - Juul, 1916 (Box-folder 89/13)
  - Juvallis, 1962 (Box-folder 89/14)
  - Jystad, 1962 (Box-folder 89/15)
  - Kaa, 1961 (Box-folder 89/16)
  - Kac--, 1964 (Box-folder 89/17)
  - Kadar, 1963 (Box-folder 89/18)
  - Kaf--, undated (Box-folder 89/19)
  - Kag--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 89/20)
  - Kag--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 89/21)
  - Kai--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 89/22)
  - Kal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 89/23)
  - Kam--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 89/24)
  - Kan--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 89/25)
  - Kap--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 89/26)
  - Kar--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 89/27)
  - Kas--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 89/28)
  - Kat--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 89/29)
  - Kau--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 89/30)
  - Kavanaugh, 1962 (Box-folder 89/31)
  - Kaw--, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 89/32)
  - Kay--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 89/33)
  - Kaz--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 89/34)
  - Kea--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 89/35)
  - Keddes, 1962 (Box-folder 89/36)
  - Kei--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 89/37)
  - Kel00, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 90/1)
  - Kefauver, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 90/2)
  - Kegg, 1964 (Box-folder 90/3)
  - Keh--, 1960; 1963 (Box-folder 90/4)
  - Kei--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 90/5)
  - Kekkonen, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 90/6)
  - Kel--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 90/7)
  - Kel--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 90/8)
  - Kem--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 90/9)
  - Kennedy, Caroline, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 90/10)
  - Kennedy, Edward, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 90/11)
  - Kennedy, Mrs. John F. (Jacqueline), 1961-1964 (Box-folder 90/12)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1960-1964 (Box-folder 90/13)
  - Kennedy, John (including family), 1961-1964 (Box-folder 90/14)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P. (Mr. & Mrs., family), 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 90/15)
  - Kennedy, Robert, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 90/16)
  - Ken--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 91/1-3)
  - Keolanui, 1961 (Box-folder 91/4)
  - Kep--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 91/5)
  - Ker--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 91/6)
  - Ker--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 91/7)
  - Kes--, 1962 (Box-folder 91/8)
  - Ketrenos, 1961 (Box-folder 91/9)
  - Kev--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 91/10)
  - Key--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 91/11)
  - Kha--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 91/12)
  - Khe--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 91/13)
  - Khovey, 1963 (Box-folder 91/14)
  - Khrushchev, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 91/15)
  - Khul, 1961 (Box-folder 91/16)
  - Kid--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 91/17)
  - Kikuchi, 1960 (Box-folder 91/18)
  - Kil--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 91/19)
  - Kim--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 91/20)
  - Kin--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 91/21)
  - Kin--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 91/22)
  - Kir--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 92/1)
  - Kis--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 92/2)
  - Klopfer, undated (Box-folder 92/3)
  - Kneisel, 1961 (Box-folder 92/4)
  - Kra--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 92/5)
  - Kra--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 92/6)
  - Kre--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 92/7)
  - Kri--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 92/8)
  - Krnjevich, 1961 (Box-folder 92/9)
  - Kro--, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 92/10)
  - Kru--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 92/11)
  - Kiisk, 1962 (Box-folder 92/12)
  - Kualii, 1963 (Box-folder 92/13)
  - Kub--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 92/14)
  - Kuc--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 92/15)
  - Kud--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 92/16)
  - Kue--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 92/17)
  - Kuh--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 92/18)
  - Kul--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 92/19)
  - Kum--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 92/20)
  - Kun--, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 92/21)
  - Kur--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 92/22)
  - Kus--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 92/23)
  - Kut--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 92/24)
  - Kuz--, 1963 (Box-folder 92/25)
  - Kvarsten, 1962 (Box-folder 92/26)
  - Kve--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 92/27)
  - Kwan--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 92/28)
  - Kwon, 1964 (Box-folder 92/29)
  - Kyle, 1963 (Box-folder 92/30)
  - Lab--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 92/31)
  - Lac--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 92/32)
  - Lad--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 93/1)
  - Laf--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 93/2)
  - Lag--, 1960-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 93/3)
  - Lahr, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 93/4)
  - Lai, 192; 19646 (Box-folder 93/5)
  - Lajarrige, 1961 (Box-folder 93/6)
  - Lak--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 93/7)
  - Lal--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 93/8)
  - Lam--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 93/9)
  - Lam--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 93/10)
  - Lan--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 93/11-13)
  - Lap--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 93/14)
  - Lar--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 93/15-16)
  - Las--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 93/17)
  - Lat--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 93/18)
  - Lau--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 93/19)
  - Leighton, 1964 (Box-folder 94/1)
  - Lew--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 94/2)
  - Lew--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 94/3)
  - Ley--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 94/4)
  - Lezak, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 94/5)
  - Lib--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 94/6)
  - Lic--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 94/7)
  - Lid--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 94/8)
  - Lie--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 94/9)
  - Lig--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 94/10)
  - Lil--, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 94/11)
  - Lim--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 94/12)
  - Lin--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 94/13-14)
  - Lit--, 1964 (Box-folder 94/15)
  - Lodge, 1964 (Box-folder 94/16)
  - Lon--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 94/17)
  - Lon--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 94/18)
  - Loo--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 95/1)
  - Lop--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 95/2)
  - Lor--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 95/3)
  - Los--, 1963 (Box-folder 95/4)
  - Lot--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 95/5)
  - Lou--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 95/6)
  - Lov--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 95/7)
  - Low--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 95/8)
  - Loy--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 95/9)
  - Lozier, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 95/10)
  - Lub--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 95/11)
  - Luc--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 95/12)
  - Lud--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 95/13)
  - Luc--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 95/14)
  - Luf--, 1961 (Box-folder 95/15)
  - Luiten, 1960 (Box-folder 95/16)
  - Lull, 1926 (Box-folder 95/17)
  - Lum--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 95/18)
  - Lun--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 95/19)
  - Lurcott, 1964 (Box-folder 95/20)
  - Lus--, 1960 (Box-folder 95/21)
  - Lut--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 95/22)
  - Luven, 1963 (Box-folder 95/23)
  - Luxon, 1963 (Box-folder 95/24)
  - Lybarger, 1964 (Box-folder 95/25)
  - Lyd--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 95/26)
  - Lyle, 1962 (Box-folder 95/27)
  - Lyman, 1961 (Box-folder 95/28)
  - Lyn--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 95/29)
  - Lyo--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 95/30)
  - Lyseng, 1962 (Box-folder 95/31)
  - Maas, 1961 (Box-folder 96/1)
  - Mab--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 96/2)
  - MacA--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 96/3)
  - McAr--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 96/4)
  - MacC--, 1960-1961; 1963-1964 (Box-folder 96/5)
  - MacD--, MacE--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 96/6)
  - MacF--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 96/7)
  - MacG--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 96/8)
  - MacK--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 96/9)
  - MacL--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 96/10)
  - MacM--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 96/11)
  - MacN--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 96/12)
  - MacA--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 96/13)
  - MacP--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 96/14)
  - MacR--, 1961; 1964 (Box-folder 96/15)
  - McB--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 96/16)
  - McC--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 96/17-21)
  - McC--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 97/1-2)
  - McD--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 97/3)
  - McD--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 97/4)
  - McE--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 97/5)
  - McF--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 97/6)
  - McG--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 97/7-8)
  - McG--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 97/9)
  - McH--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 97/10)
  - McI--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 97/11)
  - McKay--McKenna, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 97/12)
  - McKenney--McKirdie, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 97/13)
  - McL--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 98/1)
  - McM--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 98/2)
  - McNab--McNau--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 98/3)
  - McNe--McNu--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 98/4)
  - McP--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 98/5)
  - McQ--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 98/6)
  - McR--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 98/7)
  - McS--, 1964 (Box-folder 98/8)
  - McT--, 1961 (Box-folder 98/9)
  - McV--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 98/10)
  - McW--, 1963 (Box-folder 98/11)
  - Mac--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 98/12)
  - Mad--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 98/13)
  - Mae--, 1964 (Box-folder 98/14)
  - Mag--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 99/1)
  - Mag--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 99/2)
  - Mah--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 99/3)
  - Mai--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 99/4)
  - Maj--, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 99/5)
  - Mak--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 99/6)
  - Mal--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 99/7)
  - Mal--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 99/8)
  - Mal--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 99/9)
  - Mam--, 1963 (Box-folder 99/10)
  - Man--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 99/11)
  - Man--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 99/12)
  - Man--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 100/1-2)
  - Map--, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box-folder 100/3)
  - Mar--, 1960; 1962-1963 (Box-folder 100/4)
  - Mar--, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 100/5)
  - Mar--, 1961; 1963 (Box-folder 100/6)
  - Mar--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 100/7)
  - Mar--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 100/8)
  - Mar--, 1960-1961; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 101/1)
  - Mar--, 1960; 1962-1964 (Box-folder 101/2)
  - Mar--, 1961 (Box-folder 101/3)
  - Mar--, 1961 (Box-folder 101/4)
  - Mar--, 1960; 1962 (Box-folder 101/5)
  - Mar--, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 101/6)
  - Mar--, 1962 (Box-folder 101/7)
  - Mar--, 1964 (Box-folder 101/8-9)
  - Matthews, 1964 (Box-folder 101/10)
  - Mer--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 102/1)
  - Mer--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 102/2)
  - Merrill, Mellisa, 1964 (Box-folder 128/38)
  - Metz, 1964 (Box-folder 102/3)
  - Meyer, 1964 (Box-folder 102/4)
  - Mil--, 1964 (Box-folder 102/5)
  - Mineo, undated (Box-folder 102/6)
  - Montesanto, 1964 (Box-folder 102/7)
  - Morse, 1964 (Box-folder 102/8)
  - Mostert, 1964 (Box-folder 102/9)
  - Mumford, 1964 (Box-folder 102/10)
  - Mundt, undated (Box-folder 102/11)
  - Myers, 1964 (Box-folder 102/12)
  - Nabors, 1964 (Box-folder 102/13)
  - Nagi, 1964 (Box-folder 102/14)
  - Nelson, 1964 (Box-folder 102/15)
  - New--, 1964 (Box-folder 102/16)
  - Nivin, undated (Box-folder 102/17)
  - Nixon, Julie & Tricia, 1964 (Box-folder 102/18)
  - Noble, 1961 (Box-folder 102/19)
  - Nordon, undated (Box-folder 102/20)
  - Nye, undated (Box-folder 102/21)
  - O'Br--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 102/22)
  - O'Buckly, 1964 (Box-folder 102/23)
  - Ogilvie, 1964 (Box-folder 102/24)
  - Olo--, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 102/25)
  - Olsen, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 102/26)
  - Olsen, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 102/27)
  - O'Ma, 1960; 1962-1963 (Box-folder 102/28)
  - Omd--, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 102/29)
  - Olm--, 1962 (Box-folder 102/30)
  - Onassis, Tina (and Marquess of Blanford), 1961 (Box-folder 102/31)
  - O'Ne--, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 102/32)
  - Onosanya, Christiana, 1962 (Box-folder 102/33)
  - Oos--, 1963 (Box-folder 102/34)
  - Opatoshu, 1961 (Box-folder 102/35)
  - Oponowecz, 1963 (Box-folder 102/36)
  - Osb--, 1961-1964; 1966 (Box-folder 103/1)
  - Osg--, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 103/2)
  - Osinski, 1962 (Box-folder 103/3)
  - Osl--, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 103/4)
  - Osmond, 1963 (Box-folder 103/5)
  - Ossenkop, 1961 (Box-folder 103/6)
  - Ost--, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 103/7)
  - O'Sulllivan, 1962 (Box-folder 103/8)
  - Oswald, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 103/9)
  - Ota, 1963 (Box-folder 103/10)
  - Othus, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 103/11)
  - Otis, 1962 (Box-folder 103/12)
  - O'Toole, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 103/13)
  - Otsea, 1964 (Box-folder 103/14)
  - Ott--, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 103/15)
  - Ouchi, 1962; 1964 (Box-folder 103/16)
  - Ouderkirk, 1964 (Box-folder 103/17)
  - Ouellette, 1961 (Box-folder 103/18)
  - Ourston, 1960 (Box-folder 103/19)